{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Doesn't Mary want to go to that movie? \" Yes, but she says ___ tonight.\"",
      "a": "she'd not rather go",
      "b": "she'll rather not go",
      "c": "she'd rather not go",
      "d": "she won't rather go",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Would rather + V \n- Would rather + not + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": " Did you criticize him for his mistakes?  \" Yes, but ___ it.\"",
      "a": "I'd not rather",
      "b": "I'd rather not have done",
      "c": "I'd better not do",
      "d": "I'd rather not doing",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\nRemember:\n\n- Would rather + have + p.p\n\n- Would rather + not + have + p.p",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "In fact, Mary would rather have left for San Francisco ___ in Los Angeles.",
      "a": "by staying",
      "b": "than stay",
      "c": "to stay",
      "d": "than have stayed",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- Would rather ..... than ...",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are you going to be there? \" If I ___ , I'll let you know. \"",
      "a": "am",
      "b": "will be",
      "c": "would be",
      "d": "do there",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- If I am = If I am going to",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who's taken away my cookies? \" I ___ \"",
      "a": "won't",
      "b": "do",
      "c": "have",
      "d": "am",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Has taken -&gt; I have",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is natural that an employee should ___ his work on time.",
      "a": "finishes",
      "b": "finishs",
      "c": "can finish",
      "d": "finish",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- It is natural + that + S +(should) + V ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is extremely necessary that you ___ that honesty is the best policy.",
      "a": "realizing",
      "b": "realize",
      "c": "will realize",
      "d": "can realize",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n\n- It is necessary + that + S + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is important that they ___ their reservations before Friday.",
      "a": "confirm",
      "b": "confirms",
      "c": "will confirm",
      "d": "must confirm",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n\n- It is important + that + S + V",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is great pity that she ___ have done such a thing.",
      "a": "would",
      "b": "must",
      "c": "should",
      "d": "didn't",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n\n- It is a great pity + that + S + should + have + p.p",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I am sorry that Tom ___ be so weak.",
      "a": "can",
      "b": "would",
      "c": "may",
      "d": "should",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n\n- should be so weak",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "3",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}